{
    "id": "1:0x03506eD3f57892C85DB20C36846e9c808aFe9ef4:1262",
    "protocol": 1,
    "pointer": "bafkreibsbl3vy4lru53xryay4lgdhmgjf3nyiu2uvvcc5qb7lfo2uchmp4",
    "data": {
        "title": "Ephemery Testnet",
        "description": "Ephemery is an automatically reset testnet, a novel approach to public testnets. It enables a single testing infrastructure consisting of ephemeral networks with deterministic parameters. Each network iteration is created by a specified function which deterministically generates new genesis states.\n\nThis kind of testnet can provide an alternative environment for short-term testing of applications, validators and also breaking changes in client implementations. It avoids issues of long running testnets which suffer from state bloat, lack of testnet funds or consensus issues. Periodically resetting the network back to genesis cleans the validator set, returns funds back to faucets while keeping the network reasonably small for easy bootstraping.\n\nTest your applications, validators, client implementations or contribute to the testnet at ephemery.dev.\n\nIt has been running since December 2022 and is maintained only by community. Testnet is described in EIP-6916 and currently being implemented in Ethereum clients.\n",
        "website": "https://ephemery.dev",
        "userGithub": "taxmeifyoucan",
        "projectGithub": "ephemery-testnet",
        "bannerImg": "bafkreihzod2furn2ncylndiso44x6rhicv44m2oxtgqn27m4ize3jhdvwy",
        "bannerImgData": {},
        "credentials": {
            "github": {
                "@context": [
                    "https://www.w3.org/2018/credentials/v1"
                ],
                "type": [
                    "VerifiableCredential"
                ],
                "credentialSubject": {
                    "id": "did:pkh:eip155:1:0x8d3809951C7F1D18227251B0Cb047735dbf8f8fC",
                    "hash": "v0.0.0:iomGe4LFBi0NLhcR/5/55kCRCheH09rvKRjVvAUwfs0=",
                    "@context": [
                        {
                            "hash": "https://schema.org/Text",
                            "provider": "https://schema.org/Text"
                        }
                    ],
                    "provider": "ClearTextGithubOrg#ephemery-testnet#61149543"
                },
                "issuer": "did:key:z6MkghvGHLobLEdj1bgRLhS4LPGJAvbMA1tn2zcRyqmYU5LC",
                "issuanceDate": "2023-11-16T10:49:08.342Z",
                "proof": {
                    "type": "Ed25519Signature2018",
                    "proofPurpose": "assertionMethod",
                    "verificationMethod": "did:key:z6MkghvGHLobLEdj1bgRLhS4LPGJAvbMA1tn2zcRyqmYU5LC#z6MkghvGHLobLEdj1bgRLhS4LPGJAvbMA1tn2zcRyqmYU5LC",
                    "created": "2023-11-16T10:49:08.342Z",
                    "jws": "eyJhbGciOiJFZERTQSIsImNyaXQiOlsiYjY0Il0sImI2NCI6ZmFsc2V9..c45sGK0DVvHiRg08XdEwIpzGN8I1CHI8gFCvHZ8lcXKnfGrfQVrYgjcvsLjgpUkDztBhd4rjOyl2XIqb9Fy9BQ"
                },
                "expirationDate": "2024-02-14T10:49:08.342Z"
            }
        },
        "createdAt": 1700131751641
    },
    "applications": [
        {
            "id": "0xa1d52f9b5339792651861329a046dd912761e9a9-22",
            "protocol": 1,
            "pointer": "bafkreiblji4zm7jfitpeph7lcq4weif3or2mbzugfvet6hotzymh2s6kfq",
            "data": {
                "signature": "0xd86f2592d5f6e420489478807954b0afb3b16dd388c1b6e0edcee77c857390e82d4d4a1a106c9c5568acf0ba747a13fd6adf72cea496447a50553fc857e5886a1b",
                "application": {
                    "round": "0xa1d52f9b5339792651861329a046dd912761e9a9",
                    "recipient": "0x8d3809951C7F1D18227251B0Cb047735dbf8f8fC",
                    "project": {
                        "lastUpdated": 0,
                        "createdAt": 1700131751641,
                        "id": "1:0x03506eD3f57892C85DB20C36846e9c808aFe9ef4:1262",
                        "title": "Ephemery Testnet",
                        "description": "Ephemery is an automatically reset testnet, a novel approach to public testnets. It enables a single testing infrastructure consisting of ephemeral networks with deterministic parameters. Each network iteration is created by a specified function which deterministically generates new genesis states.\n\nThis kind of testnet can provide an alternative environment for short-term testing of applications, validators and also breaking changes in client implementations. It avoids issues of long running testnets which suffer from state bloat, lack of testnet funds or consensus issues. Periodically resetting the network back to genesis cleans the validator set, returns funds back to faucets while keeping the network reasonably small for easy bootstraping.\n\nTest your applications, validators, client implementations or contribute to the testnet at ephemery.dev.\n\nIt has been running since December 2022 and is maintained only by community. Testnet is described in EIP-6916 and currently being implemented in Ethereum clients.\n",
                        "website": "https://ephemery.dev",
                        "bannerImg": "bafkreihzod2furn2ncylndiso44x6rhicv44m2oxtgqn27m4ize3jhdvwy",
                        "metaPtr": {
                            "protocol": "1",
                            "pointer": "bafkreibsbl3vy4lru53xryay4lgdhmgjf3nyiu2uvvcc5qb7lfo2uchmp4"
                        },
                        "userGithub": "taxmeifyoucan",
                        "projectGithub": "ephemery-testnet",
                        "credentials": {
                            "github": {
                                "@context": [
                                    "https://www.w3.org/2018/credentials/v1"
                                ],
                                "type": [
                                    "VerifiableCredential"
                                ],
                                "credentialSubject": {
                                    "id": "did:pkh:eip155:1:0x8d3809951C7F1D18227251B0Cb047735dbf8f8fC",
                                    "hash": "v0.0.0:iomGe4LFBi0NLhcR/5/55kCRCheH09rvKRjVvAUwfs0=",
                                    "@context": [
                                        {
                                            "hash": "https://schema.org/Text",
                                            "provider": "https://schema.org/Text"
                                        }
                                    ],
                                    "provider": "ClearTextGithubOrg#ephemery-testnet#61149543"
                                },
                                "issuer": "did:key:z6MkghvGHLobLEdj1bgRLhS4LPGJAvbMA1tn2zcRyqmYU5LC",
                                "issuanceDate": "2023-11-16T10:49:08.342Z",
                                "proof": {
                                    "type": "Ed25519Signature2018",
                                    "proofPurpose": "assertionMethod",
                                    "verificationMethod": "did:key:z6MkghvGHLobLEdj1bgRLhS4LPGJAvbMA1tn2zcRyqmYU5LC#z6MkghvGHLobLEdj1bgRLhS4LPGJAvbMA1tn2zcRyqmYU5LC",
                                    "created": "2023-11-16T10:49:08.342Z",
                                    "jws": "eyJhbGciOiJFZERTQSIsImNyaXQiOlsiYjY0Il0sImI2NCI6ZmFsc2V9..c45sGK0DVvHiRg08XdEwIpzGN8I1CHI8gFCvHZ8lcXKnfGrfQVrYgjcvsLjgpUkDztBhd4rjOyl2XIqb9Fy9BQ"
                                },
                                "expirationDate": "2024-02-14T10:49:08.342Z"
                            }
                        }
                    },
                    "answers": [
                        {
                            "questionId": 0,
                            "question": "Email Address",
                            "type": "email",
                            "hidden": true,
                            "encryptedAnswer": {
                                "ciphertext": "UrQq2QEqIPyyEN0INniqAAsPlmHC2+19xMggMSkdWDa765Otopd2oexHTNxm/CYc",
                                "encryptedSymmetricKey": "2a3d4f886f104c46b88860500f7a9f955dd59a9a7813a229a77257009cdd3c256be5240155ce404130ccefd78f5fef087239b606fc6f42095075ecfc25b2c433ebddf148d25e33270a92825ca433978bb128a1c516104a19a3f96cd31e81cfb7062f4fe70a1c275844327ad11d7f85ef8ab5807651130db88586ae50bc0d09f60000000000000020d4f31ffdd498d77aee23ab4389bcb3419cdf01facc1a0c39f2a68cb3ef31489a076cd78e0f2ddba8d765fd2904cd35a6"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 1,
                            "question": "Project GitHub Repo (Not Team Page)",
                            "type": "link",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "https://github.com/ephemery-testnet/ephemery-resources"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 2,
                            "question": "Telegram Handle (you can answer N/A)",
                            "type": "short-answer",
                            "hidden": true,
                            "encryptedAnswer": {
                                "ciphertext": "ue+rUiAhlC0SJwaj5VcGzZ9IR+NDVdIy5oZEzKFU10E=",
                                "encryptedSymmetricKey": "5bd86fabf80d82a9965b2fbeb97ae5139635e4b949cc987edd7a49038f5f792bfeb7651b46f20e12ab796cee1bdc3c07b437220734858b043b5a1cfddbdc5818dce9fdf709108b9ac2df859fa198912268d71ca05a1f91bbe15f0a4386c8648d778a23451eeb99ec1b8e0567c02898d64df9888e81890f0b8b230b559baf252500000000000000208cc393268eab339ca3065438d6126366ff27055f79ce0f6ae31afff36791a00aa23e663f7543d523fb5e9b56da4f0b88"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 3,
                            "question": "Gitcoin Gov Forum Handle (gov.gitcoin.co)",
                            "type": "short-answer",
                            "hidden": false
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 4,
                            "question": "Link to your Public Group Chat (Discord or Telegram )",
                            "type": "link",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": ""
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 5,
                            "question": "How is your project in support of or directly advancing the Ethereum Network\u2019s infrastructure? ",
                            "type": "paragraph",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "Creating a new space for testing Ethereum public infrastructure. "
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 6,
                            "question": "If you've participated in past grant rounds, please share any new updates or milestones from the prior months (N/A if you haven\u2019t participated previously). ",
                            "type": "paragraph",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "Since last round, Ephemery has been implemented in 4 Ethereum clients! That's the biggest news but generally more users, traction and developer attention. "
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 7,
                            "question": "How do you measure the impact of your project? Please provide examples and/or standard metrics. This might be used in future impact reports ",
                            "type": "paragraph",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "Client devs willing to support the EIP, activity on the network.  "
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 8,
                            "question": "Total Prior Funding for the project in USD",
                            "type": "number",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "500"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 9,
                            "question": "Which of the following funding sources do you have? Check all that apply",
                            "type": "checkbox",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": [
                                "Grants"
                            ]
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 10,
                            "question": "Total Team Size",
                            "type": "number",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "4"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 11,
                            "question": "How old (in Months) is the project? (We will use Twitter, domain registration, github, etc)",
                            "type": "number",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "12"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 12,
                            "question": "If you participated in past grant rounds using a different project payout wallet address, please share it here:",
                            "type": "address",
                            "hidden": true
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 13,
                            "question": "Profiles or socials of other main team members publicly associated with the project (N/A for solo founders): ",
                            "type": "paragraph",
                            "hidden": true,
                            "answer": "twitter.com/tmiychao (EF)\n\ntwitter.com/remy_roy (EthStaker)\n\ntwitter.com/pk910 (EF)\ntwitter.com/haatkinson \n"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 14,
                            "question": "Have you read and confirmed your grant abides by the Program General Eligibility Policy? https://gitcoin.notion.site/GG18-Eligibility-cb4a5754c56043d4b3ed34eddbac261c?pvs=4",
                            "type": "short-answer",
                            "hidden": true,
                            "answer": "Yes"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 15,
                            "question": "Anything else you'd like to share about your project, previous work, or other project affiliations? Anything you'd like to add that may help in determining project eligibility?",
                            "type": "paragraph",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "Public discussion is in Matrix:  https://matrix.to/#/#staker-testnet:matrix.org "
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 16,
                            "question": "Would you like to opt-in to future messages from Gitcoin for updates, information, and/or interviews? ",
                            "type": "multiple-choice",
                            "hidden": true,
                            "answer": "Yes"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 17,
                            "question": "Would you like to opt-in to us sharing your information with select third-parties for investment opportunities? ",
                            "type": "multiple-choice",
                            "hidden": true,
                            "answer": "No"
                        },
                        {
                            "questionId": 18,
                            "question": "Location/Region where the project is (primarily) based ",
                            "type": "multiple-choice",
                            "hidden": false,
                            "answer": "N/A"
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        }
    ]
}